<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rhacklette</title>
    <description>CH based FINTA cybersecurity enthusiasts
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:40:22 +0200</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 16:40:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.9.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>CTF Training</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;overview&quot;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This document outlines the training program for capture the flag (CTF) challenges that takes place every other week. The program is designed to help you learn the skills you need to pwn all the things and become a master hacker. The program is open to all skill levels, and we encourage you to work together to learn and grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;training&quot;&gt;Training&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The training program consists of sessions that take place every other week and cover a variety of CTF topics, including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Web security&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reverse engineering&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Binary exploitation&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Forensics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cryptography&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each session will include a mix of lecture, hands-on exercises, and discussion. Participants are encouraged to bring their own laptops and tools to the sessions. Training will be held in-person with the option to join online. Everyone will receive a more detailed agenda when they sign up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;competitions&quot;&gt;Competitions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the training sessions, there will be four CTF competitions held throughout the year. These competitions will provide you with the opportunity to put your skills to the test and compete against other hackers from around the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-should-i-do-that&quot;&gt;Why should I do that?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The training program and CTF competitions offer a number of benefits, including:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved CTF skills&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Increased knowledge of security topics&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Opportunity to network with other hackers&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Challenge yourself&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have fun!!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;why-should-i-choose-your-training&quot;&gt;Why should I choose your training?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our training is a safe and welcoming space for FINTA individuals to learn about cybersecurity and participate in CTF competitions. We are committed to creating a non-judgemental environment where everyone can feel comfortable asking questions and sharing their ideas. Our instructors are experienced and knowledgeable, and they are passionate about helping FINTA individuals succeed in cybersecurity. We offer a variety of resources, including practice problems and tutorials, to help you learn at your own pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The training program and CTF competitions are a great way to improve your CTF skills and prepare for CTF competitions. If you are interested in security and want to pwn everything, then this program is for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do you want to join us? Contact us at &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:rhacklette@defcon-switzerland.org&quot;&gt;rhacklette@defcon-switzerland.org&lt;/a&gt; and we’ll tell you the next steps to be added to the participants list!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 20:40:25 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/updates/2023/05/19/ctf-training.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/updates/2023/05/19/ctf-training.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Code of Conduct</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;code-of-conduct-for-rhacklette&quot;&gt;Code of Conduct for Rhacklette&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We, Rhacklette, previously known as WoSec ZH, are committed to creating a safe and respectful space for all members of our community. As a group of female, intersex, non-binary, trans and agender (FINTA) people in Security, our goal is to provide a protected space for gender minorities in the security industry, including professionals, students, and career changers. We want to create a network in Switzerland where people feel safe, understood, and supported. We value diversity and aim to build a community where everyone can learn, have fun, and share their passion for security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To ensure that our community remains a safe and inclusive space for everyone, we have established the following terms of conduct:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Respectful Behavior&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All members of Rhacklette are expected to treat each other with respect and dignity. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination, harassment, or bullying based on gender, race, ethnicity, religion, age, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by law. We expect all members to communicate with each other in a professional and respectful manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Confidentiality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We understand that many members of our community may be working on sensitive projects or have access to confidential information. Therefore, we expect all members to respect each other’s privacy and to maintain confidentiality as appropriate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Protection of Minorities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhacklette is committed to protecting the rights and safety of all members, especially those from minority communities. We do not tolerate any form of discrimination, harassment, or bullying based on gender, race, ethnicity, religion, age, sexual orientation, or any other characteristic protected by law. We encourage all members to report any instances of discrimination, harassment, or bullying to the Rhacklette leadership team. We will investigate all complaints promptly and take appropriate action to ensure the safety and well-being of all members. We also encourage all members to be mindful of their language and behavior, and to promote a culture of respect and inclusivity in the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Participation in CTFs with Rhacklette CTF team&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rhacklette CTF team activities are exclusive to members of the Rhacklette community. To ensure fairness, all members who participate in Rhacklette CTF activities are expected to follow the rules and regulations set forth by Rhacklette CTF team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workshops/presentations for Rhacklette members&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We organize workshops/presentations for Rhacklette members to improve our skills in the security industry. We expect all members who attend these events to be respectful to the presenters and to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Networking events&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We organize networking events both internally and with external partners. We expect all members who attend these events to be respectful to each other and to represent Rhacklette positively.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monthly Dinner&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We organize monthly dinners for members of Rhacklette. We expect all members who attend these events to be respectful to each other and to communicate with each other in a professional and respectful manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compliance with Laws&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All members of Rhacklette are expected to comply with all applicable laws and regulations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;consequences-of-violating-the-terms-of-conduct&quot;&gt;Consequences of Violating the Terms of Conduct&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Violations of the terms of conduct will not be tolerated. Depending on the severity of the violation, Rhacklette may take disciplinary action, including but not limited to, warning, suspension, or termination of membership.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;conclusion&quot;&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We hope that these terms of conduct will help create a safe and respectful environment for all members of Rhacklette. We value diversity and are committed to building a community where everyone can learn, have fun, and share their passion for security.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 07 Apr 2023 18:34:25 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/updates/2023/04/07/code-of-conduct.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/updates/2023/04/07/code-of-conduct.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>updates</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
